<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>I drink and I know things</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/</link><description>A collection of random knowledge</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:44:09 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://idaikt.sporkify.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Connect Paypal to Mollie</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/how-to-connect-paypal-to-mollie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:44:09 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/how-to-connect-paypal-to-mollie/</guid><description>How to connect your PayPal Account to Mollie Log in to Mollie Dashboard Settings &amp;gt; Profiles &amp;gt; Desired Profile Activate the toggle next to PayPal, should look like this: Click the button, get redirected to PayPal, enter PayPal Business email Then login normally There might be a permissions screen Finally, there should be a confirmation: Looks like this when you click the button and go back to Mollie</description></item><item><title>Server to Server Credit Card Tokenization</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/server-to-server-credit-card-tokenization/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:44:48 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/server-to-server-credit-card-tokenization/</guid><description>Server to Server Card Tokenization with Mollie Mollie in theory has an endpoint for server-to-server card tokenization. In order to have this explained to you, you have to provide a valid PCI DSS Attestation of Compliance.
This endpoint is, unfortunately, not suitable for card tokenization from an App context, as the Access-Control-Allow-Origin HTTP Header prevents this (I think, I don&amp;rsquo;t really do frontend). See the Further Reading sections for In-App alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Webhook 401 Htaccess</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/webhook-401-htaccess/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:11:45 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/webhook-401-htaccess/</guid><description>Webhook calls fail with 401 Unauthorized The merchant probably is using a .htaccess file to restrict access to their stage environment. In order for our webhooks to get delivered, the merchant needs to add our IP addresses to the allow-list.
How to add IP addresses to the allow list See here.
What are Mollie&amp;rsquo;s IP addresses? See our help center</description></item><item><title>Magento 2 State vs Status</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/magento-2-state-vs-status/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:30:05 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/magento-2-state-vs-status/</guid><description><![CDATA[Magento 2: Status vs. State Ah yes, the joy of Magento&rsquo;s &ldquo;Status vs. State&rdquo;. It&rsquo;s actually funny, if it wasn&rsquo;t so sad. And also the slight dyslexia (and/or lack of command of the Latin language) of the person who wrote the response doesn&rsquo;t help either.
Let&rsquo;s think this through. Capitalized nouns indicate Magento concepts. fixed width font indicates a fixed technical term.
There is State: Orders have States. State denotes what technically currently is happening to the order (eg.]]></description></item><item><title>Accounting With Mollie Fundamentals</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/accounting-with-mollie-fundamentals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 11:55:19 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/accounting-with-mollie-fundamentals/</guid><description>Accounting with Mollie In the following, I will explain how, from my point of view, accounting for Mollie payments should be done by default (my accounts are only borrowed from SKR04 as an example)
Chart of accounts 4000 Income 69999 Customer 1300 Receivables from Mollie 1460 Payments in transit 1700 Bank 6850 Costs of monetary transactions Import of orders and payments (accounts receivable), triggered by the event &amp;ldquo;New order&amp;rdquo; Import of orders from Shop/ERP: Here a posting record Debtor to Revenue is created, for example: 100€ 69999 to 4000: Import of payment from Mollie (here it is important that the payment has also already been made, so there is also a capture at Klarna): Receivables against Mollie to debtor, 100€ 1300 to 69999: The debtor is now credited and the receivable against Mollie has increased.</description></item><item><title>Mollie Loves Pwa</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/mollie-loves-pwa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 11:45:07 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/mollie-loves-pwa/</guid><description>Webinar: Mollie loves PWA &amp;ldquo;Mollie loves PWA&amp;rdquo; was a webinar held in September 2021 on PWA technologies specifically for Magento 2.</description></item><item><title>Technology Fundamentals Http</title><link>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/technology-fundamentals-http/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 11:46:57 +0100</pubDate><author>Florian Bender</author><guid>https://idaikt.sporkify.net/technology-fundamentals-http/</guid><description>Webinar: Technology fundamentals - HTTP In this webinar HTTP is explained. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most fundamental web technologies, and the basis for RESTful APIs:</description></item></channel></rss>